{
    "Idle": [
        {
            "Front": "0, 0",
            "Side": "0, 0",
            "Back": "0, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 0",
            "Side": "0, 0",
            "Back": "0, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 1",
            "Side": "0, 1",
            "Back": "0, 1"
        }
    ], 
    "Emotes": [
        {
            "Front": "0, 0",
            "Side": "0, 0",
            "Back": "0, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 0",
            "Side": "0, 0",
            "Back": "0, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 2",
            "Side": "6, 2",
            "Back": "0, 2"
        }
    ], 
    "Sitting": [
        {
            "Front": "0, -2",
            "Side": "0, -8",
            "Back": "0, -9"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, -7",
            "Side": "0, -8",
            "Back": "-1, -8"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 2",
            "Side": "-3, 0",
            "Back": "0, 1"
        }
    ], 
    "Walk": [
        {
            "Front": "0, 0",
            "Side": "0, -1",
            "Back": "0, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 0",
            "Side": "0, 0",
            "Back": "0, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, -1",
            "Side": "0, 0",
            "Back": "0, -1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 0",
            "Side": "0, 0",
            "Back": "0, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 0",
            "Side": "0, -1",
            "Back": "0, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 0",
            "Side": "0, 0",
            "Back": "0, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, -1",
            "Side": "0, 0",
            "Back": "0, -1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 0",
            "Side": "0, 0",
            "Back": "0, 0"
        }
    ], 
    "Run": [
        {
            "Front": "0, 1",
            "Side": "-2, 0",
            "Back": "0, 4"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 0",
            "Side": "-2, -1",
            "Back": "0, 3"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 1",
            "Side": "-2, 0",
            "Back": "0, 4"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 3",
            "Side": "-2, 2",
            "Back": "0, 6"
        }, 
        {
            "Front": "0, 1",
            "Side": "-2, 0",
            "Back": "0, 4"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 0",
            "Side": "-2, -1",
            "Back": "0, 3"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 1",
            "Side": "-2, 0",
            "Back": "0, 4"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 3",
            "Side": "-2, 2",
            "Back": "0, 6"
        }
    ], 
    "Jump": [
        {
            "Front": "0, 0",
            "Side": "0, 0",
            "Back": "0, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, -3",
            "Side": "-3, -3",
            "Back": "0, -3"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 0",
            "Side": "0, 1",
            "Back": "0, 4"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 3",
            "Side": "0, 3",
            "Back": "0, 6"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, -1",
            "Side": "0, -1",
            "Back": "0, 2"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, -3",
            "Side": "-3, -3",
            "Back": "0, -3"
        }
    ], 
    "Climb": [
        {
            "Front": null,
            "Side": null,
            "Back": "1, 5"
        },
        {
            "Front": null,
            "Side": null,
            "Back": "1, 4"
        },
        {
            "Front": null,
            "Side": null,
            "Back": "0, 6"
        },
        {
            "Front": null,
            "Side": null,
            "Back": "-1, 5"
        },
        {
            "Front": null,
            "Side": null,
            "Back": "-1, 4"
        },
        {
            "Front": null,
            "Side": null,
            "Back": "0, 6"
        }
    ], 
    "Combat 1h - Idle": [
        {
            "Front": "1, 1",
            "Side": "-2, 0",
            "Back": "0, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "1, -1",
            "Side": "-3, -2",
            "Back": "0, -2"
        }
    ], 
    "Combat 1h - Halfslash": [
        {
            "Front": "-3, 1",
            "Side": "5, 1",
            "Back": "-1, -3"
        },
        {
            "Front": "1, -1",
            "Side": "-7, -1",
            "Back": "0, 1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "-3, 2",
            "Side": "-10, -2",
            "Back": "-3, 2"
        },
        {
            "Front": "-4, 2",
            "Side": "-14, -2",
            "Back": "-3, 3"
        },
        {
            "Front": "-4, 2",
            "Side": "-14, -2",
            "Back": "-3, 3"
        },
        {
            "Front": "1, -1",
            "Side": "-7, -1",
            "Back": "0, 1"
        }
    ],
    "Combat 1h - Slash": [
        {
            "Front": "-3, 1",
            "Side": "5, 1",
            "Back": "-1, -3"
        },
        {
            "Front": "1, -1",
            "Side": "-7, -1",
            "Back": "0, 1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "3, -1",
            "Side": "-9, -2",
            "Back": "-4, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "4, -1",
            "Side": "-10, -2",
            "Back": "-6, -1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "4, -1",
            "Side": "-10, -2",
            "Back": "-6, -1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "4, -1",
            "Side": "-10, -2",
            "Back": "-6, -1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "1, -1",
            "Side": "-7, -1",
            "Back": "0, 1"
        }
    ],
    "Combat 1h - Backslash": [
        {
            "Front": "-3, 1",
            "Side": "5, 1",
            "Back": "-1, -3"
        },
        {
            "Front": "1, -1",
            "Side": "-7, -1",
            "Back": "0, 1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "3, -1",
            "Side": "-9, -2",
            "Back": "-4, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "4, -1",
            "Side": "-10, -2",
            "Back": "-6, -1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "4, -1",
            "Side": "-10, -2",
            "Back": "-6, -1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "4, -1",
            "Side": "-10, -2",
            "Back": "-6, -1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "6, -1",
            "Side": "-8, -2",
            "Back": "-7, -1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "3, -1",
            "Side": "-3, -2",
            "Back": "-5, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, 1",
            "Side": "1, 0",
            "Back": "1, 1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "-1, 2",
            "Side": "4, 1",
            "Back": "3, 1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "-1, 2",
            "Side": "4, 1",
            "Back": "3, 1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "-1, 2",
            "Side": "4, 1",
            "Back": "3, 1"
        }
    ], 
    "Legacy - Swing": [
        {
            "Front": "0, 0",
            "Side": "0, 0",
            "Back": "0, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "0, -2",
            "Side": "-1, -2",
            "Back": "-1, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "-1, -1",
            "Side": "-1, -1",
            "Back": "-2, 0"
        },
        {
            "Front": "1, 0",
            "Side": "-2, 0",
            "Back": "1, 1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "2, 0",
            "Side": "-2, 0",
            "Back": "2, 1"
        },
        {
            "Front": "2, 0",
            "Side": "-2, 0",
            "Back": "2, 1"
        }
    ]
}